

#### **CONTACT**

**(L)** 01777608508

🔀 nazrulislamtusar@gmail.com

https://tusharportfolio.pvaatoz.com/

Dill Mohammed Road, Dhaka Uddan,

Mohammedpur, Dhaka - 1207

#### **SKILLS**

I have experienced with developing website and web applications both Static and Dynamic. I am a full stack web developer with four year experience.

HTML	95%
CSS	85%
JavaScript	76%
JS Framework	60%



ReactJs	75%
РНР	70%
PHP Framework	45%
MySQL	85%
Node.Js	65%
Laravel	35%

### **RESUME OF**

# Nazrul Islam Tushar

Web Developer and Software Engineer



#### **CAREER SUMMARY-**

I am a punctual, responsible and hard working person. I worked as a computer operator in my home city before. I worked as a web software developer online as a co- Freelancer.

I have worked developing my university course project. I made many kinds of web page templates on my own. I have good working experience in a coaching institute.

I have a research work in Artificial Intelligent, and I developed an automation system for vehicle monitoring management by advance learning.



#### WORK EXPERIENCE-

 PVAIT 2021 - 2022

I worked with **PVAIT** as a backend developer and database designer for two years. I also work as a frontend developer for their website.

• ITPVA 2020 - 2021

I worked for **ITPVA** as a full stack web developer. I developed their Complete website for their company for up to two years.

 USASERVICE24 2019 - 2020

I worked for **USASERVICE24** as their full stack web developer. Besides, I designed and developed database for their system for two years.



#### **EDUCATIONAL QUALIFICATIONS**

 Bachelor of Sciences (B.Sc) 2017 - 2022

I have completed my graduation in Computer Science and Engineering from Bangladesh University of Business and Technology (BUBT). Mirpur-2, Dhaka-1216 with CGPA: 2.89 out of 4.00

 Higher School Certificate (H.S.C) 2015 - 2016

I have completed my Higher School Certificate from Boshurhat Government Mujib College, Companiganj, Noyakhali with GPA 2.19 out of 5.00



I can design and develop a desktop application for an entire company including database with so many Programming languages and frameworks.

95%
70%
55%
80%
57%
88%
73%



I did so many research work for my academic work. I have experienced with Machine Learning Deep Learning and Data Science. I know several Advanced programming Languages and framework.

Machine Learning With Python	67%
Artificial Neural Network With Python	54%



I have also some experience with developing android application with java and flutter.

Flutter For Mobile App	35%
JAVA & XML For Mobile App	45%

$\equiv$	My Other's Qualifications bellow
<b>C</b> 4	4 XX7 */*

Content Writing	93%
Logo Design, Banner Design, Card Design, ID Card Design	65%
MS EXCEL/Google Sheet	92%
MS Office/Google Doc	96%
Power Point	94%

#### Secondary School Certificate (S.S.C) 2014 - 2016

I have completed my Secondary School Certificate from Kabirhat Model Junior High School, Kabirhat, Noyakhli with GPA 5.00 out of 5.00

# PERSONAL INFORMATION -

: Md. Mostofa Father name : Halima Khatun Mother name : 20 january 1998 Date if Birth

Religion : Islam Gender : Male **Marital Status** : Single Nationality : Bangladeshi

Permanent Address : Kabirhat, Noyakhali



## Language Proficiency -

Language	Reading	Writing	Speaking
Bangla	Best	Best	Best
English	Best	Best	Better
Hindi	None	None	Better



#### Other's Experience -

I have knowledge in problem solving. I have attended so many competitive programming event. And I have been solved up to 30 problem in deferent site's problem named CordeForces.com, CodeChef.com, HeakerRank.com, HeakerEarth.com, uvaonlinejudge.com etc. I have a profile on stoptalk.com



#### My Hobbies -

Programming, Watching Movies, Web Series and Travelling.

I undersigned, declaring that the information provided in this Curriculum Vitae is true. I always ready to submit the necessary evidence/papers as required. I am very much interested and I truly need this job, I am well skilled and a few experienced. So I believe I can do my job perfectly with my hard work, patients and what I know.

For more about me, visit my personal website: (link bellow)

https://tusharportfolio.pvaatoz.com/